[
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I am a vegetarian, ___ my whole family eats meat.",
			"optionA":"whereas",
			"optionB":"where",
			"optionC":"as",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"You can post that letter ___ you're going past the post office.",
			"optionA":"yet",
			"optionB":"since",
			"optionC":"though",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I'll be there, ___ I may be late.",
			"optionA":"even",
			"optionB":"while",
			"optionC":"although",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Even ___ they played badly they still won quite easily.",
			"optionA":"though",
			"optionB":"so",
			"optionC":"if",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He looks qualified for the job. ___ he's fluent in Spanish.",
			"optionA":"What's extra",
			"optionB":"What's more",
			"optionC":"What's add",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"I don't want to go and ___, I haven't been invited.",
			"optionA":"in any situation",
			"optionB":"in any matter",
			"optionC":"in any case",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He was very tired; ___ he went on walking.",
			"optionA":"nevertheless",
			"optionB":"despite",
			"optionC":"although",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"___ the rain, we still went to the park.",
			"optionA":"Thus",
			"optionB":"Despite",
			"optionC":"Nevertheless",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"The mirror was curved, ___ it made objects look farther",
			"optionA":"still",
			"optionB":"since",
			"optionC":"thus",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"Texting while driving is dangerous, ___, it is also illegal. ",
			"optionA":"and furthermore",
			"optionB":"and since",
			"optionC":"and though",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"His face is serious but ___ very friendly.",
			"optionA":"because",
			"optionB":"nonetheless",
			"optionC":"despite",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"John bought the watch, ___ the fact that it was expensive.",
			"optionA":"whereas",
			"optionB":"however",
			"optionC":"despite",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"He's an acclaimed painter who is ___ a sculptor.",
			"optionA":"likewise",
			"optionB":"like",
			"optionC":"likely",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"question":
		{
			"prompt":"It was early, ___ we were all ready for bed after our long hike.",
			"optionA":"while",
			"optionB":"yet",
			"optionC":"still",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]